A sky blue champagne.
The color of tears.
I'm so blessed to have met someone like you.
A hue that perfectly expressed Sayaka.
My days with Sayaka...
were filled with nothing but happiness.
Or so, they were supposed to be.
I vowed to protect her.
How can I be sure there's no ill intent
behind his "good intentions"?
An event to disrupt
the picture-perfect wedding.
- Sayaka!
The suspects who could have
orchestrated this hell...
I have my circumstances.
are the groom, Kazuomi Hayashida...
the bride's mother, Kaori Wakamatsu...
the bride's friend, Chie Hashimoto...
And...
- perhaps the most suspicious one of all...
- This person.
Airi?
There's something I can't overlook here.
[SS-studio]
I know you're in there.
I'll be back.
Was that a client?
I remember seeing her at your exhibition.
Don't tell me she's a stalker?
I hear it's a real issue for younger artists.
If you're in trouble, I'll help, alright?
It's none of your business, Hayashida.
I adjusted the colors of that photo
sent with the threat.
It should help a bit with readability.
On the left... this is...
Most likely Sayaka, right?
Yeah, you're right.
It's definitely Sayaka.
What's this on the right, a rock?
Maybe a trash bag...
Can't you make it any clearer?
No can do.
The original photo was blurry to begin with.
It's like they took it this way on purpose.
You make a fair point.
Is Sayaka wearing a sailor uniform here?
Looks like it.
I get it now.
That's why you suspect Airi,
her friend from school.
This alone isn't incriminating evidence.
- Hey, quit it -
- You're amazing, Sakuraba!
Alright, now I'm certain.
The individual who sent this photo
has a clear grudge against Sayaka.
And the sender, Airi Ozaki,
also poisoned her drink.
What I wanted to talk about
were these reviews.
[Tastes fine,
but the worker's attitude is awful]
Here, look.
This is the patisserie Sayaka worked at.
Airi looks especially photogenic here.
She obviously edited the picture.
Take a look at this.
[Tastes fine,
but the worker's attitude is awful]
Haven't you noticed anything?
[airi_Oz - Posts]
[June 21st, 2025]
Seriously?
This time, I'm coming with you.
You're not getting anything done alone.
I just want to solve the mystery,
and get back to my routine life.
Thanks.
Alright! We'll uncover Airi Ozaki's evil deeds.
Sachiko!
Is he searching for the culprit
for his beloved wife?
Or to remove himself
from the list of suspects?
We've got a tailgater behind us.
They think their flashy car is so great.
Maybe they really need to go.
Number one or number two...
What do you think?
You've got a vivid imagination.
I drive a used, compact car.
I deal with tailgaters all the time.
I plan to buy something better
when I get rich.
What's a photographer's annual salary?
Ever heard of "tact", Hayashida?
I was just asking.
You said you wanted a nice car.
I make less than 4 million yen a year.
Though I work solely as
a commercial photographer now,
I eventually want to branch out,
and treat my work as art.
Do you know Helmut Newton?
He's a role model of mine.
I always thought it would be nice
to take such charged shots like his.
I just haven't found a subject
who particularly inspires me.
I can't turn down commercial work
because I need the money.
But if I only shoot for others,
I'll lose my personal touch.
Didn't realize I was driving
with a famous photographer in the making.
You're putting a damper on my spirits.
I never had any dreams like you, Sakuraba.
So I admire your drive.
Sayaka's, too.
Sayaka hoped to become a violinist, right?
She practiced every day
instead of messing around like other kids.
I imagine she was serious about it.
Did she offer to play
at the ceremony herself?
No, that was her mother's request.
I wonder if Sayaka
really wanted to become a violinist.
What?
[Limited Edition Strawberry Smoothie]
Airi.
Airi?
Kazuomi.
Hey there.
Thank you for making time for us.
Of course. I'm sorry it had to be a weekday.
No worries. This is Sakuraba,
who I mentioned over the phone.
He would appreciate your advice
as a tax counselor.
Isn't that right?
You used me as an excuse.
"Excuse"?
- Shall we head on in?
- Right.
- Your coffees.
- Thank you.
Here you go.
Sorry, were you not a coffee drinker?
No, coffee's fine.
My sincere condolences
for the wedding, and Sayaka.
I appreciate the introduction to a client,
but please understand if I seem out of it.
Airi.
We didn't call you here today
to discuss taxes.
We came to ask about your negative reviews
written about Sayaka.
"The employee here is incompetent.
She's slow, and practically inaudible."
"I question her work ethic."
I'm sorry, what?
You wrote these reviews, did you not?
No, of course not.
You're not fooling us.
I cherish Sayaka.
I would never slander her. She's my -
"Dear friend"?
That's right.
I've been there for her,
ever since we were in high school.
Y-You're...
I can't believe you would resort
to such lies and cheap tricks.
I'm leaving.
So this is what people look like
when they snap back.
What?
This is a photo from your account.
It was uploaded the same day
this review was posted.
[June 7th, 2025]
The date and location are exactly the same.
It's a coincidence.
It happens multiple times.
Here's another "coincidence".
Same date, and location as each review.
Only the reviewers themselves differ.
You must have several burner accounts.
All to bash on Sayaka's work.
I'm impressed you can keep track
of so many personas.
I told you, I had no hand in this.
These reviews die down from November to May.
Tax firms get busy around that time.
Ozaki.
Are you familiar with the concept
of disclosing personal information?
These reviews are clearly aimed at Sayaka.
They would be filed as excessive harassment.
I plan on introducing Hayashida to a lawyer
who excels in this sort of case.
A lawyer, for something like this?
But of course.
You insist you're innocent,
so what else can we do?
We'd want to settle this peacefully,
for Sayaka's sake.
But if the culprit won't budge...
then we'll have to bring this to court.
Guilty as charged.
Yes, I wrote those reviews.
But it was all for Sayaka.
Two canelé, coming right up.
T-To go?
The employee here is incompetent.
She's slow, and practically inaudible.
I question her work ethic.
No, not that one.
I was only telling her
she grabbed the wrong cake.
I'm so sorry.
But then she began crying,
and conversing became impossible.
She made me feel like the bad guy.
I'm so sorry, sir.
These cakes taste great,
but I won't be coming again.
If she doesn't fix her work ethic,
she really ought to quit.
You're lying.
"Lying"?
You're making biased accusations against her.
I never lied.
I only wrote the truth.
Sayaka was doing her best.
But she wasn't doing enough.
A seasoned worker like her
ought to do her job well.
And crying in front of a customer?
That's no way for an adult to act.
Kind words won't change her attitude.
Let alone advice from a friend.
So I thought to advise her in other ways.
Sayaka needed critique from a third party
to see her own shortcomings.
You were so cruel to her.
Don't be so quick to call it cruelty.
I wrote those reviews for Sayaka's sake.
Airi.
Do you feel no shame in what you've done?
Ultimately, this is an issue
of Sayaka's mental state.
If you think these reviews
are what sent Sayaka to a therapist,
then you're wrong.
Sayaka always went crying to a doctor
whenever something went wrong.
Though given how Sayaka's mother is,
I'm sure it stemmed from issues at home.
I only wanted to strengthen
her fragile mentality.
But Sayaka lost her chance to change
because she began seeing you.
You're too soft on her, Kazuomi.
Your constant sympathy is of no help to her.
Sayaka needs someone to protect her.
She can't just cling to men all her life.
This is exactly why she's never changed.
It's about time she learns
to become independent.
I take it you know
Sayaka worked at a ConCafe.
Did you know she had relationships
with several of her customers?
She sought out solace in dating apps as well.
Excuse me.
This is a bit much. He's Sayaka's husband.
I'm informing him because he's her husband.
Don't act like you have good intentions.
You send us a threat,
and say it's all for Sayaka?
I've had enough.
Is this why you poisoned Sayaka?
Poison? What poison?
Is that why Sayaka collapsed?
You won't fool us twice.
This isn't our high school uniform.
If you recall the picture from earlier...
See, look. Our uniform was a blazer.
I didn't know Sayaka before high school.
Neither did Chie.
We wouldn't have a photo like this.
I'm sure you must pity "poor Sayaka".
But that's not love. It's nothing at all.
You're only looking down on her.
How dare you...
I am Sayaka's best friend.
I would never poison her.
I only corrected her weaknesses,
from a place of love.
Everything I've done, is for Sayaka's sake.
What a woman.
Airi Ozaki looked nothing like herself
from high school.
They were practically different individuals.
I'd reckon she got plastic surgery.
Plastic surgery?
She likely craves superiority,
in all aspects of her life.
Why?
She most likely has a complex of sorts.
With her twisted sense of justice,
Airi Ozaki sends Sayaka
into the depths of despair.
What a fantastic friendship indeed.
I thought she was a friend of Sayaka.
I thought she was a good person.
To think she'd be such a villain.
A villain, huh?
Those with good intent often look down on
the very people they're helping.
But Airi Ozaki won't ever see her faults.
Because she never had ill intentions.
I was sure she was the culprit.
I suppose we were off the mark.
It wasn't Chie.
And it wasn't Airi Ozaki, either.
Which only leaves one individual.
The only suspect left is Sayaka's mother,
Kaori Wakamatsu.
But what if Kazuomi Hayashida
knew everything of his wife's past?
[Kazuomi Hayashida]
I take it you know
Sayaka worked at a ConCafe.
She had relationships
with several of her customers.
She sought out solace in dating apps as well.
Sayaka.